{
    "subject": "resource/Westfield_Middle_School",
    "predicate": "property/postcode",
    "object": "MK40 4HW",
    "human_readable": "Westfield Middle School's postcode is MK40 4HW.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9884250164031982,
            "question": "Is MK40 4HW the correct postcode for Westfield Middle School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9682152271270752,
            "question": "Is there a school with the postcode MK40 4HW?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9653565883636475,
            "question": "Which school has a postcode of MK40 4HW?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8412399291992188,
            "question": "What is Westfield Middle School's postcode?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7945884466171265,
            "question": "What are the numbers in Westfield Middle School's postcode?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7798054218292236,
            "question": "What is the format of Westfield Middle School's postcode?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.730648398399353,
            "question": "Could you provide the postcode for Westfield Middle School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6658858060836792,
            "question": "What information does MK40 4HW represent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6624948382377625,
            "question": "If you were sending mail to Westfield Middle School, what postcode would you use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5716739892959595,
            "question": "Where is Westfield Middle School located?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Westfield Middle School's postcode is MK40 4HW.",
            "html": "dbpedia_683_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were sending mail to Westfield Middle School, what postcode would you use?",
            "html": "dbpedia_683_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What information does MK40 4HW represent?",
            "html": "dbpedia_683_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could you provide the postcode for Westfield Middle School?",
            "html": "dbpedia_683_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_683_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_683_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_683_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_683_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_683_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_683_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_683_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_683_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_683_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_683_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that the postcode for Westfield Middle School is MK40 4HW, which directly supports the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}